sdzsafaripark.org 2018-08-31

# Privacy Policy | San Diego Zoo Safari Park

Website privacy policy: [www.sandiegozoo.org](http://www.sandiegozoo.org/), [www.sdzsafaripark.org](http://www.sdzsafaripark.org/), [www.sandiegozooglobal.org](http://www.sandiegozooglobal.org/)  
rev. October 22, 2015

**OVERVIEW**

The Zoological Society of San Diego (ZSSD), which does business as San Diego Zoo Global, operates [www.sandiegozoo.org](http://www.sandiegozoo.org/), [www.sdzsafaripark.org](http://www.sdzsafaripark.org/), and [www.sandiegozooglobal.org](http://www.sandiegozooglobal.org/) and recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of the users of these websites. Except when express permission is specifically and knowingly provided by you, the website user, the ZSSD collects no personally identifying information about individuals. The name, address, and payment information (if applicable) that the user might provide when using these websites may be processed or disclosed by the ZSSD as permitted under the website’s Terms of Use, which the user agrees to upon utilizing the information and services of [www.sandiegozoo.org](http://www.sandiegozoo.org/), and/or [www.sdzsafaripark.org](http://www.sdzsafaripark.org/), and/or [www.sandiegozooglobal.org](http://www.sandiegozooglobal.org/). It is necessary to gather certain information from you in order to provide an efficient and pleasant shopping experience. By using a number of security technologies in our websites, we maintain, as a priority, the privacy of your information. We also adhere to strict policies preventing the unauthorized use of your personal information. Finally, please note that this policy applies only to [www.sandiegozoo.org](http://www.sandiegozoo.org/), [www.sdzsafaripark.org](http://www.sdzsafaripark.org/), and [www.sandiegozooglobal.org](http://www.sandiegozooglobal.org/) and not to our sponsors’ or partners’ websites to which we link.

**INFORMATION COLLECTION AND SHARING**

We utilize cookies, which are small pieces of information sent to your web browser by a website that you visit. Used as a method of tracking, cookies also enable the ZSSD to relate a visitor’s use of ZSSD information to any information that the visitor may have specifically and knowingly provided to the ZSSD. Any such voluntarily provided information, if applicable, may be used by the ZSSD for editorial, marketing, or promotional purposes. You can set your browser to not accept cookies from this and other websites you may visit. By doing so however, some websites or portions of websites may not function properly. By using our websites and not disabling cookies, you consent to allowing their use for the purposes described in this policy.  

In addition to cookies, information we collect from you is used to help us monitor site usage and traffic patterns of our customers to the extent that it serves our legitimate business purposes. The ZSSD will maintain appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity, and privacy of your information. Statistical aggregate information, as well as personal information, is collected for internal and administrative purposes. Any public disclosure of aggregate information regarding site usage and traffic, which is necessary for business marketing and advertising purposes, is always devoid of any personally identifying information.

The personally identifiable information that you provide to us and information about your order may be combined with other personally identifiable information from our records and other sources. This information will be used to make our future marketing efforts more efficient. This information may also be shared with our third party service providers and other marketers whose products or services we feel may be of interest to you.

The use of cookies and basic information can be used for the targeting and retargeting of messages across various websites for internet-based advertising. This includes sharing cookie data and basic information with third party advertising vendors for the optimization of campaigns. Examples of information which may be automatically collected include type of operating system, type of browser, your IP address, your website visits before and after coming to our sites, UDID (mobile devices), links clicked, and standard server log information.

To opt out of information sharing for the purpose of advertising, please contact 619-718-3000 with your request.

**CHILDREN AND PRIVACY**

The ZSSD is concerned about protecting children’s privacy. If you are 12 years of age or younger, we do not want your personal information. Please do not submit any personal information to us. There may be some areas within [www.sandiegozoo.org](http://www.sandiegozoo.org/), [www.sdzsafaripark.org](http://www.sdzsafaripark.org/), and/or [www.sandiegozooglobal.org](http://www.sandiegozooglobal.org/) where people may post messages or provide feedback, but children are again discouraged from providing any personal information. If a visitor known to be a child (younger than 13) sends an e-mail to the ZSSD, we will only use it to respond to the e-mail and not to create profiles or otherwise retain the information.

**SECURE SHOPPING**

The Zoological Society of San Diego has incorporated the latest Internet technological standards into the design of the secure purchase areas of [www.sandiegozoo.org](http://www.sandiegozoo.org/), [www.sdzsafaripark.org](http://www.sdzsafaripark.org/), and [www.sandiegozooglobal.org](http://www.sandiegozooglobal.org/). We also monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to access, upload, or change information on the website and across the network. Under no uncertain terms, any information you send us while within the secure shipping area is protected by 128-bit “Secure Socket Layer” SSL encryption, making your transaction safe and reliable. You can tell whether you are in our secure shopping area by viewing the lock or key at the bottom of your browser—an unlocked or broken key (depending on your browser) means you are in an unsecured area.  
Shopping on the Internet is safe, and online credit card transactions are no more risky than other means of shopping. Our encryption methods make credit card fraud even more difficult than mail or phone orders, or even in-person purchases. If you experience fraudulent use of your credit card as a result of using our website, notify your credit card company per its rules and procedures. Most credit card companies will either cover the fraudulent purchases or hold you liable for no more than $50.

As a standard Internet practice, should your credit card company hold you liable for some portion of a fraudulent charge, [www.sandiegozoo.org](http://www.sandiegozoo.org/), [www.sdzsafaripark.org](http://www.sdzsafaripark.org/), and/or [www.sandiegozooglobal.org](http://www.sandiegozooglobal.org/) will reimburse you for the maximum liability of $50, provided the purchase was made through our secure server.

The ZSSD needs to know your name, e-mail address, shipping address, and credit card number and expiration date in order to process and fulfill your order. We might also request additional information that you choose to submit about your interests or feedback about our site and products so that we can provide a better shopping experience for you. The name, address, and payment information that the user might provide when using [www.sandiegozoo.org](http://www.sandiegozoo.org/), [www.sdzsafaripark.org](http://www.sdzsafaripark.org/), and/or [www.sandiegozooglobal.org](http://www.sandiegozooglobal.org/) may be processed or disclosed by the ZSSD as permitted under the website’s Terms of Use, of which the user agrees to upon utilizing the information and services of the websites.

**YOUR CONSENT AND CHANGES TO POLICY**

By using [www.sandiegozoo.org](http://www.sandiegozoo.org/), [www.sdzsafaripark.org](http://www.sdzsafaripark.org/), and/or [www.sandiegozooglobal.org](http://www.sandiegozooglobal.org/), you consent to this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use. This privacy policy may be changed at any time. Please check this page periodically for any changes. Your continued use of [www.sandiegozoo.org](http://www.sandiegozoo.org/), [www.sdzsafaripark.org](http://www.sdzsafaripark.org/), and [www.sandiegozooglobal.org](http://www.sandiegozooglobal.org/) following the posting of any changes constitutes your acceptance of the changes.
